<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on Child</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on Child</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/getting-started/</guid><description>This page is a quickstart and doesn&amp;rsquo;t describe all of Child capabilities. Register your user Identify yourself Register a channel Child behaves differently from other services like Anope or Atheme: instead of having multiple service accounts (NickServ, ChanServ, OperServ&amp;hellip;), C handles everything under its name.
This page describes how to register an account, identify yourself, register and manage simple access control on it.</description></item><item><title>Managing a channel</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/manage-channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/manage-channel/</guid><description>To execute on this, you need to have registered your account first. Register a channel Manage access lists Moderating Register a channel You now have your account and want to register your channel. To do so, you need to be +o (op) on a channel that is not registered yet.
/join #newchannel By entering the channel, the server will give you +o.</description></item><item><title>Managing your account</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/manage-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/usage/manage-account/</guid><description>Child&amp;rsquo;s NickServ is accessible via /msg C nick.
The first thing to do if you didn&amp;rsquo;t already is to register your account:
/msg C nick register PASSWORD EMAIL You will then receive a notice from C:
C (cserve@geeknode.org): You are now registered. User mode [+r] by services.geeknode.org You are now logged in as test. (nick!ident@host) These messages might appear in a status window or tab in your client. For instance, in weechat, it&amp;rsquo;ll be in the first buffer.</description></item></channel></rss>