<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Commands on Child</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/</link><description>Recent content in Commands on Child</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bot Commands</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/bot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/bot/</guid><description>Child has commands you can use in channels it&amp;rsquo;s present in.
!admin !ban !dehalfop !dehalfopall !deop !deopall !deowner !deprotect !devoice !devoiceall !halfop !halfopall !rkb !kb !rkick !kick !op !opall !owner !protect !seen !tb !tblist !topic !unban !voice !voiceall !admin Display online irc operators.
!ban Ban someone
!dehalfop Take halfop
!dehalfopall Dehalfop everyone</description></item><item><title>Chan Commands</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/chan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/chan/</guid><description>You can always check each command help using /msg C chan help COMMAND access flags levels addbot assign banlist botlist clearbans clearchan clearmodes dehalfop delbot deop devoice drop entrymsg halfop info invite kick op register resync set aop autolimit avoice axxflags enablemask enftopic founder mass mlock noauto nojoin private protectops secure strictop suspend topic unassign unbanall unsuspend voice access Syntax: HELP CHAN ACCESS FLAGS for help about chanflags Syntax: HELP CHAN ACCESS LEVELS for help about old levels system The CHAN ACCESS command automatically adapts himself regarding to the AXXFLAGS channel option.</description></item><item><title>Host Commands</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/host/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/host/</guid><description>Host commands manage vhosts for users. These commands are only available to opers.
list set list /msg C host list List all users having a vhost.
set /msg C host set ACCOUNTNAME VHOST Set a vhost for an account.</description></item><item><title>Nick Commands</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/nick/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/nick/</guid><description>You can always check each command help using /msg C nick help COMMAND drop ghost identify info link register requestpassword set cloak email hideemail master noauto password private protect timeout unlink drop /msg C nick drop [ACCOUNTNAME] Drop your account.
ghost /msg C nick ghost ACCOUNTNAME PASSWORD Kill a ghosted nick. This is handy when one loses connectivity and their previous session is still holding a nick.</description></item><item><title>Oper Commands</title><link>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/oper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethylix.github.io/child/commands/oper/</guid><description>These commands are only available to opers.
changelev chanlist die fakejoin fakekill fakelist fakenick fakesay fakeuser forceauth glineall glinechan global jupe killall modlist modload modunload nicklist noexpire operlist raw rehash regexpcheck restart savedb sglobal stats superadmin suspend trustadd trustdel trustlist userlist changelev Change a user&amp;rsquo;s level
chanlist Search a registered channel
die Die services</description></item></channel></rss>